(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
公演ハッシュタグ #超ゲマズ2_day2
Performance Hashtag #cho_gamers2_day2
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while for the show to begin
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ！
hololive GAMERS fes. Cho-cho-cho-cho Gamers!
みゃう
Miau
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready? No!
Perfect!
みお！みお！みお！
Mio! Mio! Mio!
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ！
hololive GAMERS fes. Cho-cho-cho-cho Gamers!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G A M E R S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G A M E R S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G A M E R S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okay!
Korone!
猫又おかゆ！
Nekomata Okayu!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
コンコン！
Kon kon!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
公演ハッシュタグ #超ゲマズ2_day2
Performance hashtag #ChoGamaz2_day2
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
ミオ
Mio
Are you ready? Go!
フブキ
Fubuki
G-A-M-E-R-S
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance begins.
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
Are you ready?
おかゆ！
Okayu!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ
hololive GAMERS fes. Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while for the start of the performance.
Are you ready?
Now!
Perfect.
Are you ready?
Now!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
WE ARE GAMERS!
コンコンキツネー！
Kon kon kitsune!
ミオーン！
Mioon!
もぐもぐおかゆー！
Mogumogu Okayu!
ころねー！
Korone!
WE ARE GAMERS!
コーン！白上フブキだぞ
Kon! It's Shirakami Fubuki.
表も裏も白上フブキ　見ての通りにしら上お化けです
Inside and out, it's Shirakami Fubuki.
As you can see, I'm the ghost Shirakami.
ズッコンバッコン始まらない
Zukkon bakkon, it won't start.
君もスタッフに入りなさい　ハイ！せーの！
You should join the staff too.
Hi! Ready, go!
ハイ！ホーイ！ハイ！ホーイ！
Hi! Hoi! Hi! Hoi!
ミオしゃー！
Mio-sha!
ププチププチだよ大神ミオだよ
Puchi puchi puchi, it's Ookami Mio.
黒髪ケモミミ狼　ミャー！
Black-haired animal-eared wolf. Mya!
ズッコンバッコン止まらなーい
Zukkon bakkon, I can't stop.
笑い出すと止まらない　ケラケラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop. Kerakera.
占い的中　暴風雨
Fortune-telling hit: a rainstorm.
壊してセットしちゃうぞ
I'll break it and set it up.
カロット占い　的中未来
Tarot reading, a future that hits home.
ホラゲー　やりたくなーい！
I don't wanna play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高！
When the four of us are together, Gamers are the best!
グラつかなければフリーズ最高！
If it doesn't wobble, freezing is the best!
目を鍛えて狙い打ち今日は
Train your eyes and take aim today.
何プレイしよう？
What should we play?
君のハートを攻略しちゃうぜ
I'm gonna conquer your heart.
択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choices and simulate.
初見も古参もダイヤだヤバ
First-timers and veterans, it's Diamond, wow!
ゲームは楽しくね！
Let's have fun with games!
ハイ！ホーイ！ハイ！ホーイ！
Hi! Hoi! Hi! Hoi!
WE ARE GAMERS!
ハイ！ホーイ！ハイ！ホーイ！
Hi! Hoi! Hi! Hoi!
いつものまったりおにぎりおかゆ
Same old chill onigiri, Okayu.
オン眉オン眉ハイカット
High-cut bangs, high-cut bangs.
ヒラヒラフラフラそこの猫だもん
Fluttering and swaying, I'm just a cat.
放っておいてよくない？
Isn't it okay to leave me be?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
A chill and slow bouncing rhythm.
全肯定全肯定いいリズム
Full approval, full approval, a good rhythm.
全肯定全肯定氷OK？
Full approval, full approval, is the ice OK?
毎日ぼくといっしょ！
With me every day!
ころねー！
Korone!
おらよ！ゆびゆびわんわん
Here you go! Yubi yubi wan wan.
パンはころころ戌神ころね
Rolling bread, Inugami Korone.
練習今日もイーティングジャガイモ
Practicing today too, eating potatoes.
そばにおるなつくけどアタッカー
By your side, friendly but an attacker.
いつもマルいインターナショナルなリアクション
Always round, international reactions.
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ハイ！試食！
First, will you offer up your fingers? Hi! Tasting time!
分かったな？ホネズキ。OK。
Got it? Bone-lover. OK.
動物の鳴き声お届け
Delivering animal sounds.
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高！
When the four of us are together, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばフリーズ最高！
When a flag is raised, freezing is the best!
腕を鍛えて狙い打ち今日は
Train your arms and take aim today.
何プレイしよう？
What should we play?
君のハートを攻略しちゃうぜ
I'm gonna conquer your heart.
ワクワクするねこの感情
This feeling makes my heart race.
大好きすぎるからやめられない
I love it too much to stop.
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I just love games!
唐突ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間よ！
Out of the blue, it's time for a Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、お宝ゲットを狙っちゃいましょう！
Respond with a loud voice and aim to get the treasure!
Are you ready? せーの！
Are you ready? One, two!
コンコン！
Kon kon!
ミョーミョー！
Myo myo!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
コンコン！
Kon kon!
ミョーミョー！
Myo myo!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
PERFECT!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高！
When the four of us are together, Gamers are the best!
いもむし行かなくても最高！
Even without plucking potatoes, it's the best!
全クリするまで諦めない
I won't give up until I've cleared it all.
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending.
君のハートを攻略しちゃうぜ
I'm gonna conquer your heart.
択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choices and simulate.
初見も古参もダイヤだヤバ
First-timers and veterans, it's Diamond, wow!
ゲームは楽しくね！
Let's have fun with games!
ハイ！ホーイ！ハイ！ホーイ！
Hi! Hoi! Hi! Hoi!
WE ARE GAMERS!
ハイ！ホーイ！ハイ！ホーイ！
Hi! Hoi! Hi! Hoi!
WE ARE GAMERS!
こうしてさいたまスーパーアリーナに、俺たちが訪れたってわけ。シャキーン！
And that's how we ended up visiting Saitama Super Arena. Shakin'!
本日もいっぱいでございますな。
There's a full house today as well!
ありがたいですな。
We're so grateful.
ありがたいことですよもう本当に。
Truly, it's something to be grateful for.
ということで。
And so...
さあ、始まりました！
Well, it's finally here!
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス、
hololive GAMERS fes.
超超超超ゲーマーズ2、DAY 2です！
Chō Chō Chō Chō Gamers 2, Day 2!
ということで、皆さん！
So, everyone!
こんこんきーつね！
Kon-kon-kitsune!
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
いやあ、さすがですね。
Wow, as expected.
どうも、なぜかゲーマーズの掛け声では「ヨシ」が入った白上です。よろしくお願いします！
Hello, I'm Shirakami, who for some reason had 'Yoshi' included in the Gamers' chant. Nice to meet you!
なぜ「ヨシ」が入ったんだ。
Why was 'Yoshi' in there?
あれ「ヨシ」だったんだ。
So that was 'Yoshi'?
「ホロトリ」に「ヨシ」をやってました。
I was doing 'Yoshi' for 'Holotori'.
練習の時、あんなの一回もしてなかった。
You didn't do that even once during practice.
突然の「ヨシ」。
A sudden 'Yoshi'.
さあ、続いては！はい！
All right, next! Here!
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
ウチウチ！ウチだよ！大神ミオだよー！
Uchi-uchi! It's me! I'm Ookami Mio!
おかしいんだよなあ。
That's strange...
大神ミオです、皆さん。今日も盛り上げよろしくお願いします！
I'm Ookami Mio, everyone. Let's get fired up today, too!
大神おじさーん！
Uncle Ookami!
おじさんじゃないんだよ！
I'm not an uncle!
そして！
And then!
はーい。みんな、行くよー。
He~y. Everyone, here we go.
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
もぐもぐー！
Mogu-mogu~!
よくできました。
Well done.
どうも、ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆです。今日もよろしくお願いします。あの、出禁にならないようにね、頑張ります。
Hello, I'm Nekomata Okayu from hololive GAMERS. Nice to be here today. Um, I'll do my best not to get banned.
おデコに。
On your forehead.
頑張ってください。
Good luck with that.
そして！
And then!
はーい！みんな行くよー！ジャン、ケン、ホイ！
He~y! Everyone, here we go! Rock, paper, shoot!
戌神ころね
Inugami Korone
ありがとう。みんな、行こうじゃねーよ。
Thank you. 'Let's go, everyone', my foot.
戌神ころねです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Inugami Korone! Nice to meet you!
ほいね。大谷翔平の次は...
Right. After Shohei Ohtani comes...
じゃんけん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
サザエさんよ！
It's Sazae-san!
サザエさんじゃねーよ！
I'm not Sazae-san!
もう、ころねすき、それでも全然平気だった？今、大丈夫だった？
Geez, Koronesuki, were you really okay with that? Was that all right just now?
ついて来れた？
Could you keep up?
ついて来れてるみたい。みんな優しいね。
Looks like they could. Everyone's so kind.
さすがです。ということで、改めて、
As expected. So, once again,
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス、超超超超ゲーマーズ2、DAY 2がここ、さいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕じゃ！
hololive GAMERS fes. Chō Chō Chō Chō Gamers 2, Day 2 is now open here at Saitama Super Arena!
いやなんと、DAY 1, DAY 2合わせるとなんと、3万5... 約3万5000人以上が！
Wow, would you believe it? If you combine Day 1 and Day 2, there are... about 35,000 people or more!
ということで、今日の、第... DAY 2は、なんと、1万7000人ぐらいいるらしいですよ！
And so, for today's... Day 2, there are apparently around 17,000 people!
すごい！どうなってんのもう！
Amazing! What is going on?!
すごい、上の方も、みんな、いますよ、あそこ！ほら！
Incredible, everyone's up there too, look!
見えてる？そこ。見えてる？
Can you see? Over there. Can you see?
大丈夫！大歓声が！
It's okay! We can hear the cheers!
左右も見えてました！見えてるかな？すごいですよもう！
We can see the left and right sides too! I wonder if they can see us? It's just amazing!
前回はですね、あの、ミオが来れなかった。国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども。
Last time, Mio couldn't make it. It was at the Yoyogi National Gymnasium First Gymnasium.
さらに今回は大きな、大きな、大きな場所でやらせていただくことになりまして。
But this time, we've been given the chance to perform in a much, much larger venue.
2回目やらせていただけて本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for letting us do this a second time!
前回立てなかった分、今回ステージに立つことができました！
Since I couldn't be there last time, I'm so happy to be standing on stage today!
よかった、よかった。
That's wonderful.
さて、改めてこのイベントではですね、ゲームが大好きな我々を中心に、
Now, once again, for this event, centered around us gamers,
超、超、超、超豪華なゲストの皆さんと一緒に、
alongside some super, super, super, super gorgeous guests,
様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、
we'll be challenging various game titles and
超超超超ゲーマーズとは
What is Chō Chō Chō Chō Gamers?
ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントとなっております！
delivering live performances in this premium event!
しかも今回ですね、もう皆さんお分かりかと思いますが、
And this time, as you can probably tell,
DAY 1に引き続き4人の、お揃い、Tシャツ！見て見て！可愛い！
following Day 1, all four of us are wearing matching T-shirts! Look, look! So cute!
お尻サービス。しっぽサービスね。しっぽサービス中。
A butt service. A tail service, I mean. Tail service in progress.
さあ、さらに会場ではですね、一部撮影OKなパートがありますので、そちらもお楽しみに！
And in the venue, there will be parts where photography is partially allowed, so look forward to that!
ぜひ最後まで皆さん、盛り上がっていけますか？！ありがとうございます！
Can everyone keep the energy high until the very end?! Thank you so much!
ということでね、我々ゲーマーズからも一人ずつ意気込みを言っていきたいと思いますよ。
So, each of us Gamers would like to share our enthusiasm.
最終日、まずはミオから！
Final day, let's start with Mio!
はい！えーとですね、昨日の意気込みで、あの、明日も...
Okay! Well, in my enthusiasm yesterday, I said 'tomorrow too'...
体調崩さないように頑張るっていうふうにね、言わせていただいたんですけども
I said I'd do my best not to get sick, but...
もう今日はこの会場にね、あのーもういてここのステージ立ってるということは
Since I'm already here at the venue and standing on this stage today...
どんなに体調崩そうとも帰れないということなので
it means that no matter how sick I get, I can't go home.
やめて！ 体調は大事にして！ 帰って！
Stop! Take care of your health! Please rest!
最… 最後まで、笑顔で走り切る、頑張りたいと思います！
I want to do my best to run until the very end with a smile!
みんな一緒に盛り上がってこう！
Let's all get excited together!
続きまして、おかゆー！
Next up, Okayu!
はーい！
Hi!
まぁ、昨日はね、逆打率3割を目標に大谷翔平ね、頑張ったんですけど
Well, yesterday I did my best aiming for a 0.300 reverse batting average, like Shohei Ohtani.
まぁちょっと逆に頑張りすぎて、もう微妙にデキになりかけたので
But I think I overdid it a bit, and I almost became a bit of a goner.
今日は、まぁ、ほどほどに、逆にほどほどに楽しんでいきたいと思います
So today, I want to enjoy myself moderately. Moderately, for a change.
ちなみに何割ぐらいなんですか？ほどほどは
By the way, what percentage is 'moderately'?
2.5
0.25.
昨日なんか、コムルの方々から、かなり厳しい講評を受けたんですけど
Yesterday, we received some pretty harsh critiques from the audience...
なんかテイクオフとかさ、なんかボケてますよこの猫、本当に
Like, 'Take-off' and stuff... This cat is really out of it.
またどんな、逆打率3割だろっていうことやらされたんですけど
They made me do things like, 'You're at a 0.300 reverse batting average' again.
やです、やりませーん
No way, I'm not doing it.
なんか、さいたまスーパーアリーナで歌わされたり、すすめとかさ…
I was made to sing 'Susume' and such at the Saitama Super Arena...
可愛かったよね
It was cute, wasn't it?
恥ずかしいんだよなぁ
It's embarrassing, though.
満足度は高かったです
The satisfaction level was high.
はい、ころねです！
Hi, I'm Korone!
昨日はね、ちょっと翔平のためにーとか言って、一部のころねすきがね、ちょっとさー
Yesterday, I said things like 'For Shohei,' and some of my Koronesuki fans...
おいおいおい、大谷さんばっかりかよーって、ピキピキピーマンになってたので
were like, 'Hey, is it all about Ohtani?' and got all Piki-Piki-Piman jealous.
今日は、今日はね、ころねすきのために頑張ります！
So today, I'll do my best for my Koronesuki!
あ、翔平ごめん
Ah, sorry, Shohei.
やめて！ やめて！
Stop it! Stop it!
はい！ そして白上もですね、今日もですね、たすか読み上げることが多いと思うんですけども
Yes! And I, Shirakami, will be reading out many messages again today.
その間、あの、この3人がきっといっぱい面白おかしいことやってくれるんじゃないかと思っておりますので
In the meantime, I'm sure these three will be doing lots of funny and interesting things.
白上のお話にも耳を貸しつつ、おめめはですね、あの上の大きいモニターと
So while you listen to me talk, keep your eyes on the big monitor above...
そしてあの可愛い3人を見ていただいて、最後皆さんでね、笑って帰れるといいなと思ってますので、よろしくお願いします！
and these three cute girls. I hope we can all go home laughing at the end, so please enjoy!
そして！昨日と今日行われる超超超超ゲーマーズ2は、ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
And! The 'Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers 2' event is being streamed live on ABEMA PPV!
ABEMA PPVで8/4(月)まで見逃し視聴可能！
ABEMA PPV: Catch-up streaming available until 8/4 (Mon)!
コメントのみんな見てるー？
Are you all in the comments watching?
コメント見えてるよー！ 見てるよー！
We can see the comments! We're watching!
翔平見てるー？って草って言われて… 大谷さん見てるかなーってコメントもね
People are saying 'Is Shohei watching? lol'... and 'I wonder if Ohtani-san is watching'.
配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
Streaming tickets are now on sale!
イベントが終わっても、8月4日（月）の23:59まで、何度でも見ることができます！
Even after the event ends, you can watch it as many times as you like until August 4th!
購入特典として、Day1とDay2で異なるシチュエーションの、限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
As a bonus, you'll get limited original voice dramas for Day 1 and Day 2!
①オリジナルボイスドラマ DAY1: 秘密の事前プロデュースボイス、DAY2: 内緒の打ち上げボイス
1. Original Voice Drama Day 1: Secret Pre-production, Day 2: Secret Post-production
Day1は、秘密の事前プロデュースボイス！
Day 1 is 'Secret Pre-production Voice'!
そしてDay2は、内緒の打ち上げボイス！
And Day 2 is 'Secret Post-production Party Voice'!
内緒ってどの程度内緒なんですか？
Just how secret is 'secret'?
あんなことや… そんなことまで…
Things like this... and even things like that...
あとはですね、我々からの直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
Also, a live image with a handwritten message from us is included, so please check it out!
②限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
2. Limited Live Image with Handwritten Message
さらに！昨年行われました超超超超ゲーマーズのダイジェストが、ABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
Furthermore! A digest of last year's 'Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers' is now on ABEMA Premium!
ABEMAプレミアムで昨年度のイベント hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ ダイジェスト映像配信中！
ABEMA Premium: Last year's event digest now streaming!
昨年のね、楽しかった場もね、皆さん見ていただきたいんですけども、4人でもね、頑張らせていただきましたので、その様子いっぱい見てください！
I want everyone to see last year's fun times. We four did our best, so please enjoy plenty of that!
はい、さらにさらに！イベント事後グッズの受注販売が開始中です！
And more! Pre-orders for the event's post-show goods have started!
イベントグッズ事後通販 Cyber Goods Storeで予約受付中！ 7月21日(月・祝) 23:59まで
Event Goods: Pre-orders open at Cyber Goods Store until 7/21 (Mon/Holiday)!
こちらの期間は、7月21日の23:59まで！ Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中で、10月中旬頃からお届けです！
Pre-orders are until July 21st! They're at Cyber Goods Store and deliver in mid-October!
こちらも予約したよーって人いますか？
Is there anyone who has already pre-ordered these?
あ、いるいる！ 結構買っちゃってるんじゃないの？
Oh, there are! Quite a few people seem to have bought them already!
買ってるけど、みんなほら、予約してるって。事後通販ありがとうございます！
They're buying, look! Thank you for using the post-show mail order!
そしてですね、本日販売のグッズは、全て売り切れと聞いております！皆さんありがとうございました！
And, I've heard that all the goods for sale today are completely sold out! Thank you all!
え、ランダムで、おしゲットできたかーい？
Hey, were you able to get your favorite through the random selection?
できたか、できたできた！ よかったー！ ありがとうございます！
Did you? You did! That's great! Thank you!
ま、ゲットできなかったーという方がいらっしゃいましたらね、
Well, if there's anyone who couldn't get them,
ぜひともあの事後通販で受注販売しておりますのでゲットしてくださいー！
they're available for pre-order via the after-event mail order, so please grab yours!
そしてさらにさらにさらに、もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが、NTTドコモさんのhome 5Gとコラボキャンペーン実施中でーす！
And furthermore, as some of you might already know, a collaboration campaign with NTT DOCOMO's home 5G is currently underway!
あ、来ましたねこれ。実施終わっちゃったんだ。えー、
Ah, here it is. Oh, it's already ended. Well,
デカタオルや入り口でもらえるうちわ、皆さんゲットしましたかー？
The big towels and the fans given at the entrance, did everyone get them?
ちゃんとやりましたよーって人！
Anyone who's already done that!
あ、いらっしゃいます、ありがとうございます。
Ah, there are some, thank you very much.
はい、ぜひ、あの準備万端にして最後までお楽しみくださいー！ ありがとうございます。
Yes, please get yourselves ready and enjoy the show until the very end! Thank you.
あ、すいません、こちらにですね、事後限定グッズとしましてアクリルパネルが、そういえば追加されてるんですよ。皆さん知ってました？
Oh, excuse me, for the after-event limited goods, I just remembered, acrylic panels have been added. Did everyone know?
そう、実はアクリルパネル。こちらね、あの事後限定グッズなので、
Yes, the acrylic panels. Since these are after-event limited items,
今「あ、そういえば！」って思った方が是非とも、あの、あの、ぜひゲットしてください。
those of you who just thought, "Oh, right!" please, um, um, please be sure to get them.
あの、あの、やめて！うわー！
Um, um, stop it! Whoa!
ごめんなさーい！
I'm sorry!
えーまだまだ続きますからね。えー我々ゲーマーズを応援したいという声が多かったので、
Well, there's more to come. Many of you said you wanted to support us Gamers, so...
今回のイベントで CheerSPOT さんとのコラボ決定！イェーイ！
a collaboration with CheerSPOT has been decided for this event! Yay!
誰でも簡単に、今チャージスポットの場所に我々の応援広告を出すことができます。
Anyone can easily place our support ads at ChargeSPOT locations.
ぜひともね、これ、あの白上も割と日頃利用させていただいておりますので、うれしいですね。ありがたい。
I'm really happy about this since I often use them myself. It's much appreciated.
じゃ、この会場内にもですね、設置してあるのを見たと思うんですけども、あんな感じでですね、すごく綺麗に広告出せますので、
You probably saw them set up inside this venue as well, but you can display ads beautifully like that,
よろしければよろしくお願いします。
so if you're interested, please do!
えーさらに埼玉スーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初お披露目させていただきました。
Furthermore, we're unveiling life-size figures for the first time here at Saitama Super Arena.
3月のエキスポ会場で発表されたふぶみお等身大に続きまして、おかころのフィギュアも発表されました。見てくれましたか？
Following the life-size FubuMio announced at the Expo in March, the OkaKoro figures have also been announced. Did you see them?
見てくれましたかー？
Did you see them?
かわいい！かわいい！
So cute! So cute!
また昨日から新作フィギュアがブシロードECから受注開始ということで、皆さん、予約したかー！
Also, pre-orders for the new figures started yesterday on Bushiroad EC, so, did everyone pre-order them?!
しろー！
DO IT!
めちゃめちゃ可愛かったですよね。ガチ可愛かった。ね！
They were really cute, weren't they? Seriously cute. Right?
イベントの開催を記念しまして、8月7日までにご予約してくれた方には特典のステッカープレゼントだそうです。
To celebrate the event, those who pre-order by August 7th will receive a bonus sticker.
欲しい欲しい。持ってねー。
I want one, I want one. Please take mine.
そしてですね、おかころ出たんですけども、ふぶみおが終わっちゃったーと思ってたんですが、なんと！
And though the OkaKoro ones came out, I thought FubuMio's pre-orders had ended, but...!
期間限定でふぶみおの追加予約も開始してます！
additional pre-orders for FubuMio have also started for a limited time!
最高！最高！
Awesome! Awesome!
お願いします。ぜひともゲーマーズ4人揃えれる方は揃えてみろ！
Please do. If you can collect all four Gamers, then go for it!
さて最後に、カンダフル様による協賛企業グッズ、超超超超ポップコーンと超超超超グリルチキンでーす！
And finally, from our sponsor Kandaful, the Cho Cho Cho Cho Popcorn and Cho Cho Cho Cho Grilled Chicken!
チキン！チキン！
Chicken! Chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことでして、
The design features the key visual of this event all over,
ポップコーンは税込1000円、缶詰は税込1500円で販売でーす。
with popcorn at 1,000 yen and canned goods at 1,500 yen including tax.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味。缶詰めはグリルチキンになってます。イェーイイェーイイェーイ！
The popcorn is salted caramel flavor, and the canned goods are grilled chicken. Yay yay yay!
これポップコーンの方にはランダムトレカがついてるそうなのでよろしくお願いします。
The popcorn also comes with a random trading card, so please check it out.
食べてる食べてる。
I'm eating it, I'm eating it.
なんと！え、サイバーグッズストアではこちらのポップコーン and 缶詰めが完売になってしまったー！
Wait! Oh, the popcorn and canned goods have already sold out on the Cyber Goods Store!
えーー！！
Whaaat?!
な、なんですけど、なんと本日22時から追加販売が決定しました！
But, additional sales have been decided starting tonight at 10 PM!
イェーイ！！フーッフーー！！
Yay!! Whoo-hoo!!
え、こちらのグッズはですね、他のグッズと異なりまして
Now, unlike our other goods,
受注販売ではなく、数量限定商品のためご注意ください。
please note that these are limited quantity items, not made-to-order.
サイバーグッズストアの他にカンダフルの公式通販サイトでも販売してますので皆さんチェックお願いします！
They're also available on Kandaful's official site besides the Cyber Goods Store, so please check them out!
はーい！
Okay!
え、集合アクリルパネルも含めですね、事後でしか購入できないグッズなので、皆さんぜひ確認してください。
Please check out all the goods, including the group acrylic panel, as they're only available after the event.
なんか、すごいデジャブなんですけど。
I'm getting some serious deja vu here.
待っておいで、ゲーマーズ列車に乗るわよ。
Wait for me, we're getting on the Gamers train.
シュッポシュッポシュッポ、フブミオ駅、フブミオ駅、回らなきゃ、回らなきゃ、
Choo choo choo, FubuMio Station, FubuMio Station, gotta turn around, gotta turn around,
シュッポシュッポ、いってらっしゃーい、まもなく、発車、終点、終点。え、終わっちゃった。
Choo choo, safe travels, departing soon, last stop, last stop. Oh, it ended.
え、また昨日に引き続きまして、本日も韓国のライブビューイングが開催されてます！
And following yesterday, a live viewing is also being held in Korea today!
韓国の皆さん見てますかー？ アンニョンハセヨ、ヨロブン！
Everyone in Korea, are you watching? Hello, everyone!
韓国の方もですね、集合写真いっぱい撮ってくださってて、あのポスト確認させていただきました。
I've seen the posts of the Korean fans taking lots of group photos. I checked them out.
今日もよろしくお願いします。サランヘヨ！
I look forward to today too. I love you!
さー、では早速ですね、最初に行うゲームタイトル発表していきましょうかね！
All right, let's announce the first game title right away!
はい、じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
はい！
Yes!
せーの！
Ready...
ゲーマーズ！
...Gamers!
ギャング・ビースツ！
Gang Beasts!
はい、こちらはゼリーのようにぷにゃぷにゃのキャラクターたちが、
Alright, in this game, jelly-like, squishy characters...
危険なステージでドタバタの乱闘を繰り広げる、ちょっとおバカなパーティーゲームです。
...engage in rowdy brawls on dangerous stages in a silly party game.
今回は2対2のチーム戦と、個人戦のツーマッチで対決したいと思います！
This time, we'll compete in two matches: a 2v2 team battle and an individual battle!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こちら勝利すると、頭の後ろにですね、星のバルーンが付きまーす。
If you win, a star balloon will be attached to the back of your head.
おー！
Oh!
最終的にバルーンが一番多い人が勝利となりまーす。
The person with the most balloons at the end will be the winner.
ということで、早速やっていきますよー！
So, let's get started right away!
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go go go!
最初のマッチは2対2のチーム戦ということで、
The first match is a 2v2 team battle,
チームはそうですね、先ほどあみだで決めました、
and the teams were decided earlier by Amidakuji (lottery).
フブおかチームと、ミオころチーム！
Fubu-Oka Team and Mio-Koro Team!
はい！
Yes!
ミオころかー。ということで、こっちだー。
Mio-Koro, huh? Okay, over here.
よーし、いくぞー！
Alright, let's do this!
フブおか神様MAXパワー！
Fubu-Oka God Max Power!
あってるかなー？ あってる、あってる。
Is that right? Yeah, it's right.
多分ギリギリあってる。
Probably just barely right.
ホントに？
Really?
ということで、こちらでですね、対決して行きたいと思います。
So, we'll be facing off like this.
ちょっと待って！ なんか、なんかないんですか？
Wait a second! Isn't there... isn't there something else?
え、何がですか？
Eh, like what?
え、なんかこう、掛け声とかチーム名とか、
You know, like a shout or a team name...
ありますよ！
We have one!
え、じゃあ教えてください！
Eh, then please tell us!
まずはー、
First,
お姉ちゃんのおかゆとー、
The big sister, Okayu...
妹のフブちゃんでーす！
...and the little sister, Fubu-chan!
おー、いいじゃーん！
Oh, that's nice!
いいじゃないですかー！
That's good!
せーの！
Ready...
二人合わせてヤングコシマエ！
...and together we are Young Koshi-mae!
いいですか？
Is that okay?
ダメです！
It's not!
ダメだ、あかん！
No way, that's bad!
なんか弱み握られてない？
Is she holding something over you?
なんかちょっと握られてたかも知らん。
She might have had a little something on me.
ちょっとね、身内の空気に流されている。
I'm being swept away by the family vibe.
はい、準備できたから、ほら。後ろにコントローラーが。
Alright, we're ready, look. The controllers are in the back.
あー、はいはいはい。持ちます、持ちます。いやらしい。
Ah, right, right. We'll take them. How nasty.
自分らのカラー取ってね、ちゃんと。
Pick your own colors, okay?
はい、ということで、
Alright, so,
おったー！
Found it!
はい、ありがとうございます。
Yes, thank you.
コントローラーでやっていきたいと思います。ではゲーム画面に切り替えて下さーい！
We'll play with these controllers. Now, please switch to the game screen!
なんか両手上げてますけど。
Everyone's got their hands up.
わー！ これ誰が誰か、みんな分かんないかな？
Whoa! I wonder if everyone knows who's who?
じゃあささっと紹介しよう。
Let's do a quick intro then.
はい。
Okay.
まずですね、これ、青い、白衣着てるのが、白上さんだそうです。どうも。
First, this blue one in the lab coat is Shirakami. Hello.
そしてそのお隣が、はい、ガン決まりのネコの被り物をしてるのが僕です。
And next to her, wearing the wide-eyed cat mask, is me.
おかゆー！
Okayu!
はい、そしてー、
Yes, and then...
なんか真っ赤っかな、えーと、ネコ耳っぽいの被ってるのがウチです。大神ミオです。
The bright red one with the... cat ears, I guess? That's me. Ookami Mio.
はい、そしてー、
Yes, and then...
ギャッハー！ みたいなやつがコーネ！
The one going 'Gyah-ha!' is Korone!
ギャッハッハ！ ギャッハー！ みたいなやつ。
Gyah-ha-ha! Gyah-ha! That kind of thing.
ということで、まずは赤と青に分かれまして、チーム戦でございます。準備いいですかー？
So, we're split into Red and Blue for a team battle. Are you ready?
おー！
Oh!
はい！
Yes!
それでは、ギャング・ビースツ1回戦、スタート！
Alright, Gang Beasts Round 1, start!
やるぞー！ 頑張るぞー！
Let's do this! Good luck everyone!
力を見せてやろう。
We'll show you our power.
いけるのか？
Can we do it?
いけるよ、負けまへんわー。
We can! We won't lose!
赤と青で応援して下さいね、どっちが勝つか。
Please cheer for Red or Blue and see who wins.
おらー！
Hah!
赤いの来たぞ、見ろ！
The red one's coming, look!
やめて！ おら！ なにこれ！
Stop! Hah! What is this?!
やばい！ やばい！ やばい！ おらー！
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out! Hah!
いやー！ こっち来た！
No! It came over here!
待って！ やめろ！ いー！
Wait! Stop! Eek!
なにこれ、なんか二人で。やめろー！
What is this? They're both... Stop it!
やめろー！ やめて！ やめてー！ おー！
Stop it! Stop! Stop it! Oh!
あぶない！ あぶない！ 待って！
Danger! Danger! Wait!
やばい、やばい、やばい！
No, no, no!
いやー！ いやー！ 頑張る！
Nooo! Nooo! I'll do my best!
待って！ おかゆー！ やばい、やばい、やばい！
Wait! Okayu! No, no, no!
ふにゃふにゃしてる、こわい。
It's so squishy, I'm scared.
待って、おかゆ、どこ？ 助けて！
Wait, Okayu, where are you? Help!
これ、どうなってるの、もう。
What's even happening anymore?!
うわー！ 何休んでるの！
Whoa! Why are you resting?!
待って！ もう死んじゃった。
Wait! I'm already dead.
待って！ やだ、見ないで！ やめて！
Wait! No, don't look! Stop!
引きずり出される！ やめてー！
I'm being dragged out! Stop it!
イエーイ！ やったー！ 勝ったー！
Yay! We did it! We won!
でもこれ二戦先取なので、二回勝ったチームが勝利ですからね。
But this is best-of-three, so the team that wins twice will be the overall winner.
おー！
Oh!
よし！ 星だ！ 星！
Alright! Stars! Stars!
もう始まってる！始まってる！
It's already started! It's started!
判定！判定！
Judgment! Judgment!
うらあ！神殿！神殿！
Oryaa! Shrine! Shrine!
ブルーの勝利
Blue Victory
ああ！やばい！やばい！
Ah! Oh no! Oh no!
数の暴力やばい！
The violence of numbers is crazy!
数の暴力やばいよね！
The violence of numbers is crazy, isn't it!
次も頑張れ！次も頑張れ！
Good luck for the next one too!
あそこに巻き込もうぜ！
Let's drag them into that!
これピンチだぞこれ！
This is a pinch! This is!
うらあ！
Oryaa!
やばい！おら！おら！
Oh no! Ora! Ora!
やべえ！
Oh crap!
何これ落ちるよ！
What is this? We're gonna fall!
落ちるよ強くなった！
We're falling! They got stronger!
おら！おら！
Ora! Ora!
落ちろ！落ちろ！落ちろ！
Fall! Fall! Fall!
逃げろ！強者！
Run! Strong one!
扉から逃げようとしてる！
She's trying to escape through the door!
あはは！
Ahaha!
やめて！落とされる！
Stop! I'm gonna be dropped!
ああ、みお！
Ah, Mio!
嫌だ！穴の横！
No! Next to the hole!
危ない！危ない！
Watch out! Watch out!
行け、行け！落とせ！
Go, go! Drop them!
落とせ！落とせ！落とせ！
Drop them! Drop them! Drop them!
助けて！嫌だ！
Help! No!
落とすぞ！落とすぞ！
I'll drop you! I'll drop you!
ほら！あはは！
Look! Ahaha!
ブルーの勝利
Blue Victory
道連れのミオンだ！
It's double-suicide Mion!
やばいこれ怖い！
This is bad, it's scary!
やばいってこれ！やったー！
This is bad! Yay!
負けたよ！
I lost!
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
負けた、負けた、勝った星の数は...
We lost, we lost, the number of stars won is...
え？負けた？
Eh? We lost?
勝った星の数は...
The number of stars won is...
1、2、3、4！
1, 2, 3, 4!
二人合わせて4つ！対するは？
Together, it's 4! As for the others?
こっちは102個！
We have 102!
嘘つけ！変な数だ！
Liar! That's a weird number!
ということで今回は、にゃんずの勝利！
So for this time, it's Nyanz's victory!
やったー！
Yay!
え、突然ですが、ここでお知らせでございます。
Uh, suddenly, but there is an announcement here.
あ、お疲れ様です！バイバイ！
Ah, thank you for your hard work! Bye-bye!
無料配信をご覧の皆様はここまでとなります。
For those watching the free stream, this is where it ends.
続きを見たい方はぜひ、ABEMA PPVにてチケットのご購入をお願いいたします。
If you want to see the rest, please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV.
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you very much!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
みたいよね！
You want to see it, right!
この後個人戦が待ってますからね！
There's an individual match waiting after this!
バチバチにやりあっていきたいと思います！
We're going to go all out against each other!
それでは、またね！
Well then, see ya!
無料パートは終了いたしました。全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free part has ended. The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
The free part has ended.
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
Check the QR code for streaming details!
Okay!
ころね！
Korone!
Okay!
I'm ready. Go!
Ready... Go!
Good lucky!
ミオ！
Mio!
Okay!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free part has ended.
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
ご購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマと
限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像がもらえる！
Purchase Bonus: Get an original voice drama and
a limited live photo with a handwritten message!
ころね！
Korone!
G-A-M-E-R-S!
I'm ready... now!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
Gamer! Gamer! Gamer! Gamer!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G... A... M... E... R... S!
ころね！
Korone!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Check the QR code for stream details!
早期購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマと限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像もらえる！
Early purchase bonus: Get an original voice drama and a live image with a limited handwritten message!